Carel Bailey Germain Papers, 1922-1998
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES VI. SUBJECTS
  - Physiology: the brain (Box 33, Folder 225)
  - Physiology: pregnancy (Box 33, Folder 226-227)
  - Politics (Box 34, Folder 228)
  - Poverty (Box 34, Folder 229)
  - Reynolds, Bertha Capen (Box 34, Folder 230)
  - School age child (Box 34, Folder 231-232)
  - School years (Box 35, Folder 233-234)
  - Schools (Box 35, Folder 235)
  - Simulations (Box 35, Folder 236)
  - Social work theory (Box 35, Folder 237-238)
  - Stress (Box 35, Folder 239)
  - Summer camp (Box 35, Folder 240)
  - Work, workplace (Box 36, Folder 241-243)
  - Miscellaneous, unidentified (Box 36, Folder 244)
- OVERSIZE MATERIAL
  - Artwork for Human Behavior in the Social Environment: An Ecological View, 1991 (Map-case Flat File:)
  - Diagram from subject file "Simulations" (Map-case Flat File:)
  - Pamphlet, "Vital Signs of a Healthy Nation", National Association of Social Workers, undated (Map-case Flat File:)